One, ten, hundred, thousand, ten thousand, hundred thousand, million.
Oh, my God.
It's an instant kill.
Shengtian Banzi held the top for so many days.
He was overtaken in an instant.
This is the world of the rich.
Why are you watching this kind of stuff too?
Where is Liang Chen?
Did he not come?
It's already been two days.
I only chose this course for him.
Donghai 183 sent a rocket.
Sigh, I still lost.
Let me check on the fans in the stream.
Wow, what's going on?
Can someone tell me what's happening?
Thank you all for the gifts.
That's it for today's stream.
Bye.
What's wrong?
I've been streaming for so long.
I've never seen such random gifting.
It is indeed unusual.
And,
most of it was sent by Donghai 183.
He's sent almost a million points.
He just entered the room.
Could it be someone I know?
Who exactly is this person?
Who is this top donor?
Such a spendthrift.
Zixi.
Actually,
I'm the top donor.
After luckily becoming
your 10,000th fan,
I felt like we were
destined for each other.
What?
The one topping the chart is Liang Chen.
Why?
What makes Yin Zixi deserve this?
I did a rough calculation.
Around hundreds of thousands have been spent.
What?
Keep your voice down, girl.
Who exactly is Donghai 183?
Why is the recent diary always a step behind?
Can't I get a little cheat code?
Still not satisfied?
Wen Lingli.
Finally caught you,
big influencer.
What do you want from me?
I heard you sing and dance in your live stream.
You are very popular among those lonely men.
My interaction with my fans,
why do you make it sound so disgusting?
Whether it's disgusting or not,
you know it in your heart.
What do you mean?
What exactly did you do to Liang Chen?
I didn't do anything to him.
Then why did he spend hundreds of thousands to support you?
He spent hundreds of thousands on me?
You're still playing dumb.
Wen Lingli.
Are you crazy?
Liang Chen,
are you bewitched?
What's wrong with you today?
Huh?
Oh.
Nothing.
You seem to be out of it.
Donghai 183
seems to be Liang Chen from our class.
Liang Chen?
Yeah.
Senior,
I want to return the money to him.
Are you sure it's him?
I...
Who do you think told Wen Lingli?
Yeah,
that person really has a big mouth.
Hao.
Do you think I
did a bad thing with good intentions?
Boss.
If there are such bad things in the future,
come to me first.
Zixi wasn't happy at all.
Really?
Didn't you watch her stream?
She didn't smile.
She used to smile a lot.
You've only watched his livestream twice, right?
What did you say?
I said, you've only watched twice.
You want me to tell her directly?
I never said that.
That makes sense.
Casting Deputy Director: Xi Chongjing
Props Assistant: Li Kunxiao
Production Vehicle: Yi Mingle
Yitong